Angel M. Demerutis

2221 W. Painted Sunset Cir. Tucson AZ, 85745 E. angel_demerutis@hotmail.com M. (520) 867 3070

Managing Director

Envisioned Managing Director driven by challenges, undertakes complex projects and continuously demonstrates competitiveness. Decreased cost of materials an average of 15 percent by building key partnerships. Increased sales 28 percent by negotiating new contracts, reducing waste and making daily decisions based on market data. Coordinated and mentored personnel throughout an organization; over 5 years of experience leading teams.

Professional Experience

Agricola Rita Rosario S.A. de C.V. Sinaloa Mexico Managing Director

April 2013- Present

- Managed entire operation
- Secured Source of funding
- Acquired key partnerships
- Administered sales
- Evaluated sales in international market
- Formulated budget analysis
- Analyzed data to make strategic decisions

Agricola Rita Rosario S.A. de C.V. Sinaloa Mexico International representative

January 2011- April 2013

- Built business relationships
- Translated from English to Spanish
- Evaluated and analyzed sales
- Coordinated logistics

O'Reilly Auto Parts 3630 N. Oracle Rd. Tucson AZ, 85705 Assistant Manager

June 2008- July 2012

- Lead a team of 5 team members
- Ensured quality service to customers
- Conducted training to new personnel
- Organized payroll schedules

Education

Bachelor in Business Administration, Northern Arizona University, Flagstaff, AZ.

Major: International Business, GPA: 3.2/4.0

Graduation Date May 2013